So we can take a taxi
I'll give you money
when I get home
Use it to go home
Okay
It's gone
I can't find
the money envelope
My pay for this month
was in there
F***, what do I do?
Um…
You can stay over
Want to sleep here?
That's unexpected
He lives alone
in a studio apartment
It's cleaner
than I thought…
Calm down
We'll eat and go to sleep
That's it
There's no cause
for alarm
Just go to bed
right away
I wasn't
expecting guests
so for food
I only have ramyeon
Lend me some
comfortable clothes
Wear some pants
you son of a b****
I'm wearing underwear
At least
give me some clothes
before you cuss me out
I can't do this
I need to kick him out
I'll look
for my money again
Hey, you should
call your parents…
Huh?
Go to sleep, you b******
F***ing a**hole
Why is he being so mean
to me?
Starting tomorrow
I'm definitely
getting rid of him